Okay, watch these videos, and then I got a story for you.
So up until today, I have had beef with Remy, because I didn't even know, guys.
She's talking about the old Remy, not the new.
Not the new and improved, and I'm so sorry.
And I'm so happy.
And it really is a testament to seeing people change and grow, and seeing how you've done
that is really empowering, and I'm happy that we could reconcile.
And she's really, like, super sweet.
I don't know how I ever.
Okay, story time.
So last night, I was talking to my dude on the phone, and I was just telling him about
how, you know, people say life is short, but life is long, because, you know, you end up
having to come back to situations that you might have thought were a wrap, but the truth
is, is, you know, there's oftentimes opportunity for reconciliation, et cetera, et cetera, because
we're still here.
So I was like, oh, let me tell you a really good story about that.
So I started telling him a story about me and Remy Ma.
So me and Remy Ma were really cool.
I was in her music video.
So I had given her, like, an award at an underground rap award show, and then shortly thereafter,
we were both on a panel for AllHipHop.com.
And I was on that panel in the best of spirits.
It was me, her, Jim Jones, and David Banner.
And someone asked her about her lyrics and, you know, kind of, like, what inspires her.
And she was just like, well, you know, I'll just kind of be doing whatever I'll be doing.
And, like, it's not like I'm really trying to, like, do anything for y'all.
And I said, well, I think what they're saying is that, like, your lyrics inspire them.
And so, you know, they're just wanting to know, like, what inspires you.
And she just turned around and was like, what would you know?
You ain't hip-hop.
Dun, dun, dun.
And I was like, what's happening?
What's happening?
And she was like, what makes you hip-hop?
And I was so taken aback.
Also because, like, we had just been cool.
Like, the other day.
So, I was like, well, you know, I'm hip-hop because.
And this is when I was doing spoken word.
And I was like, you know, I had found my creative voice and my, like, my powerful voice in hip-hop.
And she was like, you don't know nothing about hip-hop.
I'm out of here.
Don't nobody listen to your dumb poems.
So, I was crushed.
Okay?
I was crushed.
Because I also thought that we were cool.
And, listen, I am a girl's girl.
Okay?
Like, I get along with the boys.
But I love when there's a sisterhood.
Now, we then, a couple weeks later, are at the Mix Show Power Summit in Bahamas.
And that was when they used to have this event every year where, like, the DJs and the radio execs and the artists would kind of, like, all be in the same place.
Like a three-day mix and network vibe thing.
So, I'm interviewing DJ Drama.
Because, remember, I was a member of the affiliate.
So, I'm interviewing DJ Drama for allhip-hop.com.
And here comes Remy.
And she's literally heckling me as I'm interviewing him.
And she was like, she don't know.
Now, mind you, I am also, like, mindful.
Because let's just say Remy wanted to fight.
I'm going to get my ass beat.
You know, I know my capabilities in certain situations.
I am not, by any means, unaware.
So, I was like, what's happening?
Okay.
So, about maybe a few, it felt like two weeks.
But I actually don't remember how much longer it was.
But shortly after that is when she ended up in an altercation that sent her to prison for quite some time.
Fast forward.
Years and years and years and years and years later, I'm in L.A.
And I am at Hollywood Squares.
The executive producers of Hollywood Squares, Jesse Collins, Dionne Harmon, those are my really good friends.
And they're like, oh, you know, come and do Hollywood Squares.
I was like, oh, who's on the show?
And they start listing names.
They said Remy Ma.
I was like, I can't be on an episode with Remy.
Because, you know, in my mind, I'm still thinking, like, we got beef.
So, they're like, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, no problem, no problem.
I get there for the taping.
They reading off who's on my episode?
Remy.
I was like, go.
So, before you go on set, they had this, like, lounge that they created in the studio.
And that's where, like, folks would kind of mingle before we would go on set to actually shoot the game show.
So, this is also where I first met Lauren London.
And when I met Lauren London, it was literally like, hello, we're friends.
Like, you know, you just meet somebody and it's like, oh, I've been, I knew you.
It was like that.
Like, I felt like I knew Lauren in another life.
We met.
We were immediately peoples.
So, we sitting there talking.
And then she looks up.
And she's like, so picture us talking.
She's looking behind me.
And she's like, do you know Remy Ma?
And I was like, I mean, in the past, there was a beef.
And she was like, because she's staring at you from across the room.
So, these are those moments where you have to find out, like, who are you?
Okay?
What type of person are you?
Are you going to fold like a napkin?
Or is you going to stand on business?
Y'all know I'm a stand-on-business kind of gal.
So, I was like, all right then.
I'm standing.
What's good?
So, now Remy starts walking towards me.
I'm looking at her.
And she's looking at me.
And I'm looking at her.
And she was like, yo, do we got beef?
Again, you have to ask yourself, what kind of person are you?
And I am not afraid of confrontation.
Some people think that confrontation is synonymous with hostility or with aggression.
And I consider confrontation to be literally the only way for a resolution to take place.
So, whatever happens on the other side of it is its own thing.
But in order to actually get that in motion, you got to confront it.
So, I chose confrontation in that moment.
And I was like, I mean, last time I saw you, yeah, we did have beef.
This could have gone a number of different ways.
And the way that it went was so beautiful.
And she was like, damn, we had beef.
And I was like, yeah, you did this, that, the third.
And she was like, my fault, yo.
My fault.
Like, I'm sorry.
She was like, you know, they'd just be so shit from that time.
So much shit from that time that I don't even be remembering.
Because it was just, I was another person.
And so, I be having to apologize a lot.
So, I just, I just wanted to say my bad.
And that was such a beautiful, wonderful moment.
And I, this morning, was scanning through my old videos trying to find another video.
And I came across these two videos.
I didn't even know I had them.
And I just love that I captured this reconciliatory, reconciliatory, reconciliatory?
I'm glad that I captured this reconciliation.
And this beautiful display of love between two sisters.
Because I don't think we get to see that enough.
And to be quite honest, in the wake of all this madness that be going on around me and
people misrepresenting me, I love that I actually have record of love, right?
Because that's the stuff that people don't highlight.
But it's so often abundant around us.
We just have to choose to highlight it ourselves.
So, I was supposed to interview Remy for Small Doses Podcast.
I ended up having to cancel.
And we didn't get to reschedule.
But whatever the case, I just want to shout out Remy Ma.
And wherever you are in the world, I hope you are having a wonderful, beautiful day.
Support a real one.